Here
Have a taste
This is my son-in-law
brought back from a business trip to Dandong
Kiwi berries
Are they sweet?
Of course, very sweet
I can't eat them
Old Liang
No, I have diabetes
Rudy
Type 2
diabetes
Xiao Cai
I also... well
Look at this
Fine
I'll show some support
Right
Let me
pick a soft one
Okay
A specialty
Really good
Boss Li
Your son-in-law is really nice
Thinking of his father-in-law first with good food
Honest and family-oriented
Spends his earnings on his wife
If you want a good life
the woman must run the house
This son-in-law of mine
was personally promoted by me
His main strengths are
proactive and hardworking
honest and obedient
I think
in a marriage, living together
two people must respect each other
understand each other
and give each other some space
Uncles and Aunties
don't you agree?
Speak up
How do you explain this?
I
I might have slipped
An accidental operation
Make it up
You're making things up again
How is it so coincidental?
With this female friend of yours
this Qianqian
you deleted all the chat logs with her
But the chat logs with President Ma
why weren't those deleted?
And "Follow President Ma's lead"
President Ma is my direct supervisor
Don't change the subject on me
Tell me what's going on with this Qianqian
There's nothing going on between us
We are completely innocent
Your college sweetheart, right?
She always kept you as a backup, right?
I'm aware of all these details.
Didn't I voluntarily confess before we got married?
What are you mumbling about?
Listen here, Wu Yuntang.
She's already married.
Her second kid is already running errands.
Why are you still so obsessed with her?
There's one more thing.
That you aren't aware of.
She just recently got divorced.
Because of you?
No.
It has nothing to do with me.
It was her French husband.
He had an affair.
He found a mistress from Belgium.
I heard she's even a fashion model.
A model?
That's right.
Pfft.
Who cares about her messy business?
Let me tell you, Wu Yuntang.
You better behave yourself.
Did you hear she got divorced...
...and decide you want to be her backup again?
Confess honestly.
Aren't I honest enough?
In your Li family...
I never hit back or talk back.
I hand over my salary and do all the housework.
Isn't that exactly what you should do?
Why should I have to do that?
When have you ever cared about my feelings?
Have you ever respected me?
Respect you for what?
Respect you for flirting with other people?
If you're going to put it that way...
Then let me tell you something.
A few days ago...
I actually met up with Qianqian.
You— But nothing happened!
But seeing how you're acting now...
I'm actually starting to regret that.
You're hurting me!
Regret?
You regret it?
If you regret it, go find her then!
Get out!
You're telling me to get out?
This is my home too.
What do you mean "your home"?
My dad bought this house!
You...
You... I...
What are you doing?
Are you going to hit me?
I...
I want a divorce.
What did you say?
Say that again.
I...
Want a divorce.
You're bringing up divorce with me?
You are ridiculous.
This Little Wu...
He is a wolf of Zhongshan,
Ruthless once he gets his way.
I'm usually very good at judging character.
How did I miss the mark this time?
You, good at judging character?
You were the one who introduced Little Wu, right?
I saw that at work, he was...
Proactive and hardworking,
Honest and simple,
Dutiful,
And bore burdens without complaint.
It was an act.
He just wanted to suck up to you.
Looking at the situation now,
When Little Wu pursued Jiajia back then,
His motives were impure.
It was your nepotism.
You gave him an exceptional promotion.
Of course.
Actually, no.
It was my subordinates doing it out of respect for me.
It's all your fault.
Think about how many people pursued me back then.
Zhang Xiao.
Cao Yang.
Yi Zan.
Ying Di.
Who wasn't better than him?
Honestly.
Yeah.
Didn't every single one of them...
Get driven away by you?
I just saw that Little Wu was wimpy,
Honest and simple,
And could stand your temper.
It was an act.
He was faking it all.
No way.
I won't let him get away with this.
Honey,
Let's calm down first, okay?
Yes.
I think Little Wu just spoke out of anger.
How about this.
I'll call him over personally.
I'll talk to him face to face.
It's no use what anyone says.
I am definitely getting this divorce.
No.
I am very calm.
It is absolutely not an impulse.
Let me tell you,
If Jiajia wasn't so...
Obedient to me,
Making it hard for me to speak up.
Qianqian,
It was your divorce
That gave me courage.
I've decided to go crazy for love once.
Qianqian,
I have so much to tell you.
When do you have time for us to meet?
You do your thing.
I'm available whenever you call.
Little Zhang.
What's my schedule for today?
Let me take a look.
This morning,
Lunch with President Zhang of 2B1.
And the subsequent itinerary,
Is with this President Zhang,
The two of you,
Will go for a site visit together.
After this visit,
Let me see...
Hello? Who is this?
Dad.
Boss Li.
Old Li.
What is it?
About this matter...
I've really been a bit busy lately.
How about this,
I'll have my secretary schedule a time.
I'll make an appointment with you another day.
Okay.
Okay, bye-bye.
See?
Overestimated yourself, didn't you?
Here, call Uncle Ma directly.
And have him fired.
I bet that'll fix him.
Child,
if you do that,
your divorce will be set in stone.
There's no room for reconciliation.
So be it.
I don't want to be with him anyway.
Your Uncle Fan makes sense.
Don't be impulsive.
Let's hear what the folks think.
How dare you, Wu Yuntang.
You don't know how good you have it.
Marrying such a good wife like Jiajia.
And you're still not satisfied.
Let me tell you,
you deserve to be stuck with my awful daughter-in-law.
I'm telling you,
that daughter-in-law of mine...
I say, Auntie Cai,
you mean,
you agree Jiajia should divorce?
Well, I...
I didn't say that.
Didn't you...
Doesn't the old saying go,
Better to destroy ten temples
than one marriage.
If you can make do, make do.
But if worst comes to worst...
You said nothing at all.
Old Li,
I understand you.
We both have daughters.
Yes, right?
And I'm a bit better off than you.
I've been divorced.
You call being divorced "better off"?
No, I have experience.
Experience makes an expert.
Divorce,
is really no fun.
Don't do it if you can avoid it.
Of course,
if you absolutely must divorce,
then you must.
That's also like saying nothing.
No,
I've always believed,
that an unhappy marriage
is not worth maintaining.
Since Little Wu has had a change of heart,
you can't force love.
Listen to what Teacher Liu said.
Of course,
if Little Wu changes his mind back,
You also said nothing.
My suggestion,
if there is no love left,
then why not let go?
This is very normal.
Every man and woman
has the right to love or not to love.
Just say whether to divorce or not.
My suggestion is,
you can divorce,
or you can not divorce.
Divorce.
You must divorce.
You must make a clean break with that Wu Yuntang.
Dad,
I have just one request now.
Call that President Ma.
Have him strip that ungrateful Wu Yuntang
of all his titles.
This...
Here, use my phone.
You call.
Call right now.
Tell him right now.
Jiajia
President Ma and I...
used to have
many disagreements on decisions.
Now that I'm no longer in office,
making this phone call
might not work.
It...
It's really hard to say.
It might even
be counterproductive
and humiliating.
Don't you think?
So what should we do?
Just watch that ungrateful wolf Wu Yuntang
and not be able to do anything?
Sit down first.
Listen to Dad.
Listen to me.
Here's what I think.
Let's take this opportunity
to reflect on ourselves first.
Little Wu
was introduced to you by me.
I'll start with a self-criticism.
Furthermore,
well,
shouldn't you
also examine yourself?
Don't you think
that in many ways,
you could have done better?
For the situation today,
don't you bear some responsibility too?
No way.
Let me drink it. I'll drink it.
I'm drinking it. No.
Sister Li Jia, do you want a cappuccino or a latte?
I'm not drinking.
Then I'll drink it.
I'll drink that latte.
I still want to drink that latte.
I want to drink it. We agreed yesterday.
Can you two care about me for a second?
We care.
If we didn't care about your business,
why would we come here?
Sister Jia.
When I first met your husband, I said...
You can't marry an engineering guy.
Did I say that or not?
I said that too.
Give me a break. When did you two say that?
I just remember you saying...
Brother Wu is a really nice guy.
Honest and reliable.
He looks like a hidden gem.
"Hidden gem," she said that.
I want to marry someone like that in the future.
Didn't we say that just to make you happy?
Besides...
How could you believe what us kids say?
I actually believed what you kids said.
Sister Jia, you're Type A blood, right?
That means you're gullible.
And a Virgo.
A typical lovesick mind.
And my dad insisted on telling me...
How great Little Wu is...
Boundless future.
Arranged marriages cause so much harm.
And Wu Yuntang was chasing me relentlessly.
A moment of confusion.
Blinded.
Are you two making fun of me?
Or helping me come up with ideas?
And you call yourselves volunteers.
Helping you.
We're definitely on your side, sister.
Right.
Just tell us.
How to help.
How about this.
I have an idea.
I'll go find him tomorrow.
I'll give him a good scolding.
It's not appropriate for us to scold him, is it?
Besides...
What's the use of just scolding him?
That makes sense.
We still need to criticize and educate him.
Make him pull back from the brink.
Turn back to the shore.
I'll call Wu Yuntang right now.
You...
Hello.
Yes, I'm President Wu.
Who is this?
Xie Yingzi.
It's the beautiful Yingzi.
Why did you think of calling me?
Li Jia made you call, right?
That's fine.
Then send me a location, okay?
What kind of romantic luck have I stumbled into?
The beautiful Yingzi.
What made you think of summoning me alone?
Sit.
As you command.
The reason I invited you here today...
...is mainly to talk to you.
What is going on with you and Sister Li Jia?
You see?
It was Li Jia who sent you to meet me, right?
Where is she hiding?
Is she eavesdropping somewhere?
No.
No one sent me.
I wanted to ask you myself.
It's no big deal.
Why must you get a divorce?
You ask why?
You have no idea.
Being with her...
I swallow insults and act submissive all day.
Driving, running errands, cooking, washing dishes.
I might even have to kneel on the washboard.
Really.
So what?
Isn't it said that once married...
...every husband is like this?
But I've had enough!
I, Wu Yuntang...
...even if I were an AI robot...
...would have reached the moment of developing self-awareness...
...and awakening by now.
Nonsense!
You're talking nonsense!
Who are you?
Keke, right?
You were eavesdropping inside just now, weren't you?
What "had enough," what "awakening"?
Let me tell you.
That's called being fickle and having an affair.
Do you admit it or not?
Do you think we don't know about Qianqian?
Oh, you're talking about that.
I am indeed considering that aspect.
I admit it.
What can you do to me?
I...
I really can't do anything to him.
Brother Wu.
You have to have some conscience.
Think about it.
If you hadn't latched onto Li Jia back then...
...would you be where you are today?
President Wu?
That's not necessarily true.
I, Wu Yuntang...
Peking University, Tsinghua...
...I've attended them all.
Or rather, I haven't.
Why mention them if you haven't?
But I believe...
...gold will eventually be spent.
Huh?
No, eventually panic.
Shine.
Shouldn't you thank Grandpa Li for that?
For letting you shine?
You don't know Li Jia's temper.
Compared to our Qianqian's gentleness and care...
...and understanding nature...
...she is miles behind.
Nonsense!
Shut up!
We are criticizing you here!
You're not allowed to badmouth our Sister Li Jia!
What's wrong?
Can't I talk about her many flaws?
I insist on saying it.
To tell the truth...
...Li Jia...
...is just a tigress sleeping beside me.
No.
Fiercer than a tigress.
She's simply a devil, a demoness!
Wu Yuntang, you big jerk!
You
Fine
You were eavesdropping inside the whole time, right?
All right, all right, you two
I cannot win an argument with you
I am leaving
See you at the Marriage Registration Office
Fine, see you there
Whoever does not go is a little dog
Sister, sister
Jiajia, what are you doing?
Exactly, sis
There is really no room to turn back like this
Then so be it
I am definitely divorcing
Calm down
That is enough
Qianqian
What are you doing here?
Look at this
Back to being free
Congrats
I came straight from the Marriage Registration Office
You sure are decisive
How is it so fast?
It is not because of me, is it?
Of course it is because of you
Of course
My marriage with Li Jia
at its core
also had irreconcilable problems
That explains it
As long as it is not my fault, good
I really do not want to be a homewrecker
You know my happy marriage with my ex husband
was ruined by that Belgian mistress
I hate mistresses so much
I absolutely despise mistresses
Right
Mistresses are awful
Mistresses are really darn it
Darn it
Seriously
But Qianqian
I just think
you should let go of your worries
Look
In a flash we are already past thirty
If we do not chase our own happiness now
it will be too late
What you are saying really makes sense
Right?
But
if you marry me
will our marriage definitely be happy?
Since Little Wu's heart
is no longer with you,
I think it's better to let him go.
On this matter,
Dad is responsible.
Dad,
this has nothing to do with you.
Growing up,
schools had to be top-tier,
choosing a college major,
jobs had to be easy and respectable,
and a partner...
Isn't this just...
my fault?
Dad,
actually, these past couple of days,
I've been thinking too.
Wu Yuntang and that female classmate of his,
it was a bit less than love,
but a bit more than friendship.
If I hadn't kept such a close watch,
and been a bit more oblivious,
maybe it wouldn't have come to this.
True.
I'm exactly the same way.
Wanting to win every battle,
only to lose the entire war.
Daughter, you take after me.
Is that a good thing?
Jiajia,
here to see your dad again?
Uncle.
Why isn't that...
Old Liang, you...
why do you...
always have to touch a sore spot?
Can't I mention it if it's sore?
I'm welcoming our Jiajia
to join me and Rudy's divorce club.
What are you saying?
What are you talking about?
Jiajia, don't listen to Uncle Liang.
It's good that Little Wu is gone.
We'll find someone even better.
Leave finding a partner to Auntie Cai.
Okay.
Jiajia.
Little Wu?
He has a few words to say to you.
Jiajia,
I was wrong.
That Qianqian, she said I...
She...
Will you give me another chance?
How dare you, Wu Yuntang!
You have the nerve to come see me?
Right!
There's no going back for us!
Get out!
Leave the century egg behind!